안녕, 얘들아
-Hi, guys.
-Hey, Phoebe.
- 안녕, 피비
- 어떻게 됐어?
-How did it go?
-Not so good.
별로야
He walked me home and said,
" Let's do this again. "
전철역까지 데려다 주더니
우리 다시 만나죠 하더라
저런
왜, 다시 만나기로 했다면서?
그럼 좋은 거 아냐?
He said, " Let's do this again. "
That's good, right?
제대로 해석해야지
T ranslated, " Let's do this again"
means, "You'll never see me naked. "
"우리 다시 만나죠"라는 건
"다신 못 보겠네요"란 뜻이야
언제부터?
Since when?
원래 그래
남녀 사이에 통하는 말이지
Since always.
It's, like, dating language.
당신 때문이 아니란 말은
당신 때문이란 뜻이야
Like, " It's not you"
means, " It is you. "
"당신은 참 좋은 사람이에요"는
"You' re nice" means, " I'll be
dating alcoholics...
"잘난 남자들 만나보고 당신한테
얘기해 줄게요"란 뜻이지
...and complaining
about them to you. "
"우리, 다른 사람들을 만나보죠"는
벌써 만나고 있다는 뜻이야
"We should see
other people" means:
" Ha-ha, I already am! "
- 너희는 다 알고 있어?
- 그럼
Everybody knows this?
돌려서 말하는 거야
Cushions the blow.
부모님이 개를 죽여놓고 농장에
보냈다고 말하는 거랑 똑같아
Like your parents
putting the dog to sleep...
...and saying it went to a farm.
That's funny. Because our
parents actually did...
그거 재밌다
근데 우리 부모님은 진짜
우리 개를 농장으로 보내셨어
...send our dog off to live on a farm.
Ross?
오빠?
Hello! The Milner's farm
in Connecticut?
코네티켓에 있는 밀너 농장에
보냈다고 했잖아
The Milners had this
unbelievable farm.
밀너 농장이라고 기막힌
농장이 있다고 하셨어
They had horses and
rabbits to chase.
말도 있고 토끼도 있고
그래서...
And it was....
맙소사, 치치!
Oh, my God! Chi-Chi!
The One With the Thumb
죽음을 앞둔 심정이 어떠냐?
How does it feel knowing
you're about to die?
5분 후면 내 고통은 끝나지만
Warden, in five minutes
my pain will be over.
당신들은 죄없는 사람을 죽였단
죄책감에 평생 시달릴 거요
But you'll live with the knowledge
that you sent an honest man to die.
정말 잘했어
That was really good!
고마워, 계속하자
Thanks. Let's keep going.
그래, 원하는 게 뭐냐, 디몬?
So, what do you want
from me, Dimon? Huh?
I just wanna go back to my cell,
because in my cell I can smoke.
내 방으로 보내주시오
내 방에서 담배를 피워야겠소
피워버려
Smoke away!
이러니까 방에서 혼자
담배를 피우려고 하나보지?
I think this is why Dimon
smokes in his cell alone.
-What?
-Relax your hand.
왜?
손에 힘을 빼
손목을 늘어뜨려
Let your wrist go.
너무 많이 말고
Not so much!
All right. Now take a puff.
좋아, 연기를 내뿜어
Right.
좋아
좋아, 아니
이리 줘봐
-Give it to me.
-I'm not giving you a cigarette.
안돼, 담배 안 줄 거야
괜찮아
이 역을 하고 싶긴 한 거야?
It's fine. Do you want to
get this part or not? Here.
자, 이걸 담배라고
생각하지 말고
Now, don't think
of it as a cigarette.
네 손이 그리워했던
물건이라고 생각해봐
Think of it as the thing that
has been missing from your hand.
이걸 쥐는 순간 마음이 편안해
지면서 기분이 좋아지는 거지
When you hold it,
you feel right.
You feel complete.
-You miss it?
-No, not so much.
- 담배가 그리웠어?
- 아니, 별로
All right. Now we smoke.
그럼, 피운다
죽인다
Oh, my God!
이리 내놔
-Give me that!
-No. You've got options.
아냐
내 모습을 잘 봐
이렇게 피워도 되고...
You can smoke like this:
- 챈들러
- 입에 물고 그냥 피워도 되고
-Chandler
-Or hold it in your mouth.
담배 이리 줘, 어서...
Give me the cigarette!
-You try.
-Thank you.
- 그래, 네가 해봐
- 좋아, 이건 어때?
Okay, how's this?
- 나쁘진 않다
- 그래?
Okay, that's not bad.
All right, when you' re finished,
it's cool if you flick it.
휙 던져보면 더 낫겠다
휙, 휙!
All right, you keep practicing...
넌 계속 연습해
난 소파 불이나 끌게
...and I'll go put out the sofa.
난 남자 발이
기준인 줄 알았는데
I thought it was foot size.
아니, 아니, 그 거리를 정확히
말하자면 엄지손가락에서
No. It's the distance
from the tip of a guy's thumb...
검지손가락까지야
...to the tip of his index finger.
That's ridiculous.
말도 안돼
Can I use either thumb?
다른 쪽 엄지도 괜찮아?
I'd rather go with the foot theory.
난 그냥 발을 기준으로 할래
All right. Don't tell me.
좋아, 아무 말 하지 마
조이는 디카페인 카푸치노
Decaf cappuccino for Joey.
블랙 커피
Coffee, black.
Latte.
라떼
And an iced tea.
아이스티
- 나 잘하지?
- 그래, 아주 잘했어
-I'm getting good at this.
-Excellent!
원래 똑똑하잖아
Good for me!
꿈도 꾸지 말자...
절대로...
-You okay, Phoebe?
-It's not worth
괜찮아, 피비?
그래, 아니, 이럴 순 없어
내 계좌 때문에
It's my bank.
-What did they do?
-It's nothing
무슨 일 있었어?
그런 게 아니라...
I get my mail and
open their monthly "statement. "
메일을 만들어서 월별로
계좌를 확인하는데 말야!
Easy!
진정해
And there's $500 extra in my account.
근데 내 계좌에 5백달러가
더 들어있는 거야
사탄이 유혹하는구나
Satan's minions at work again!
당장 은행에 가서
따져야겠어
Now I have to go deal with them
무슨 소릴 하는 거야?
그냥 가져
-What are you talking about? IKeep it!
-It's not mine.
내 돈이 아니잖아
내가 번 것도 아닌데
그냥 가지면 훔치는 거야
If I kept it, I'd be stealing.
그냥 써버리면 쇼핑하는 것
같을 거야
But if you spent it,
it would be like shopping.
좋아, 내가 그 돈으로
비싼 구두를 샀다고 치자
Say I bought a great pair of shoes.
한 걸음 걸을 때마다
무슨 소리가 들리게?
IKnow what I'd hear with every step?
"Not mine. Not mine. Not mine. "
내 게 아냐, 내 게 아냐
Even if I was happy
and skipping, I'd hear:
기분이 좋아서 팔짝팔짝
뛰어다닐 때도
그 소리가 들릴 거야
내 게 아냐, 내 게 아냐
" Not-not mine. Not-not mine. "
그만해, 알아들었어
We' re with you. We got it.
그냥 기분이 좋지가 않아
큰 빚을 진 기분이야
I'd never be able to enjoy it.
It'd be this giant karmic debt.
챈들러, 너 뭐해?
Chandler, what are you doing?
뭐하고 있어?
What are you doing?
Oh, gross!
- 세상에
- 뭐하는 거야?
-What is this?
-I'm smoking!
담배 핀다, 담배 피워
말도 안돼
3년간 잘 참았잖아
You've been so good for three years!
그 동안의 보상이야
And this is my reward.
잠깐, 담배끊기가 얼마나
힘들었는지 생각해봐
Think about what you went
through when you quit.
Forget about you. Think about
what we went through!
So this time I won't quit.
이번엔 안 끊을 거야
꺼, 빨리
-Put it out!
-I'm putting it out!
알았어, 끄면 되잖아
안돼,
지금은 못 마시겠다
Oh, no!
I can't drink this now.
옷 갈아입으러 가야지
데이트 있거든
I'm gonna go. I've got a date.
또 알란 만나는 거야?
어떻게 돼가?
With Alan again?
How's it going?
잘 돼가고 있어
만나면 좋고 재미있어
It's going pretty good.
It's nice and we' re having fun.
- 우리 언제 소개시켜줄 거야?
- 그래
When do we get to meet him?
오늘이 월요일이니까...
절대 안돼
Let's see, it's Monday....
-Never.
-Come on!
소개해 줘
Not after what happened with Steve.
스티브 만났을 때 어쨌어?
무슨 소리야?
우리 스티브 좋아해, 섹시하잖아
What do you mean?
We love Steve. Steve was sexy!
미안
Sorry.
지금은 내 감정을 잘 모르겠어
생각할 시간을 줘
I don't know how I feel yet.
Let me figure it out.
그 담엔 소개해주는 거야?
Then can we meet him?
No.
아니, 미안해
Sorry.
조이, 그만 좀 해
Joey. Let it go.
왜 친구들한테 소개해야
되는 거냐구요
Why should they meet him?
집에 데려가면 5분도 안돼서
완전히 뭉개 버리거든요
I bring a guy home and they're like...
코요테 같은 친구들이라
약점이 보이면 가만두질 않아요
...coyotes picking off the weak
members of the herd.
이봐
Listen, as someone who's seen
more than her share of bad beef...
내 눈에 안 보여도
남들 눈엔 잘 띄는 법이거든
내 말 들어
... I'll tell you,
that is not such a terrible thing.
그렇게 큰 일도 아니네
네 친구들이잖아
다 널 위해 그러는 거야
Your friends are just
looking after you.
내가 집에 데려가는 남자를
애들이 좋아했으면 좋겠어요
I wish that once I'd date a guy
they liked.
소개를 안 하면 그럴 가능성이
눈꼽만큼도 없는 거잖아
You realize the odds of that
happening are slimmer...
-...if they never get to meet the guy.
-I know.
나도 알아요
어리광 좀 피워도 돼요?
-Can't I whimper a little bit?
-Whimper.
해봐
Okay, l' m done.
끝났어요
Let it go, Ross.
그만 잊어버려
넌 치치를 모르잖아
You didn't know Chi-Chi.
약속하는 거다?
-Do you all promise?
-We promise.
그래, 약속해
얌전히 굴게
We'll be good.
Chandler, do you promise to be good?
챈들러, 약속하지?
You can come in, but your
filter-tip buddy stays outside!
넌 들어와도 좋지만
필터 달린 친구는 안돼
안녕, 피비
"Dear Ms. Buffay.
Thank you for calling.
부페이 양, 본사의 착오를
지적해 주셔서 감사드립니다
We've credited you $500.
We' re sorry for the inconvenience...
감사의 뜻으로 5백 달러를
드리겠습니다
또한 불편을 끼쳐드린 것을
사과드리며
...and hope you'll accept
this football phone...
풋볼 전화기를 드리고자 하오니
받아주시기 바랍니다
...as our gift. "
Do you believe it?
이게 말이 되니?
천 달러에 풋볼 전화기까지
생겼어
Now I have $ 1 000
and a football phone.
어느 은행이야?
What bank is this?
Okay, it's him.
왔다
-Who is it?
-Alan.
- 누구세요?
- 알란
챈들러, 왔어
Chandler! He's here!
Do I look okay?
나 이뻐?
- 단추 좀...
- 알았어
One more button.
잠그라구
Closed! How about closed?
- 알았어, 진짜 몰랐어
- 그래
-I didn't know.
-Yeah.
Please be good.
얌전히 굴어야 돼
날 좋아하면 약속지켜야 된다
Remember how much you all like me?
안녕
Alan, this is everybody.
Everybody, this is Alan.
알란, 친구들이야
얘들아, 여긴 알란
- 안녕
- 안녕, 알란
얘기 많이 들었어요
I've heard so much about
all you guys.
고마워요
내일 전화할게요
I'll call you tomorrow. Thanks.
좋아,
알란 흉보는 시간이야
Let's let the Alan-bashing begin.
Who's gonna take the first shot?
누구부터 시작할래?
해봐
Come on!
I'll go.
내가 할게
Let's start with how he
kept picking
음식 먹는 모습부터 시작할까?
미안해, 못하겠다
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
We loved him.
- 그 친구 정말 맘에 들어
- 맘에 쏙 들어
We loved him!
- 근사한 친구야
- 정말 멋있어
Wait! We're talking about someone
I'm going out with?
잠깐, 내가 사귀는 남자를
칭찬하는 거야?
그렇다니까
향신료 이름도 다 알고
That pimento trick!
올리브를 그렇게
먹는 사람 처음이야
I'll never look at an olive
the same way again.
- 너희도 봤어?
- 그래
And did you notice?
뭐가 근사한지 알아?
웃는 모습이 예술이더라
IKnow what was great?
His smile was crooked.
그래, 예술인 마을에 사니까
-Yes! Like the man in the shoe!
-What shoe?
예술인이라니?
From the rhyme.
말장난하는 거 있잖아
"예술인 마을에 사는 그이는 웃는
모습도 먹는 모습도 예술이라네"
There was a man
With a crooked smile
Who lived in a shoe
For a while
그렇다 치고!
So I think Alan...
이제부턴 알란을 미래의 남자
친구들에 대한 기준으로 삼자
...is the yardstick by which
future boyfriends will be measured.
Future boyfriends?
미래의 남자친구들이라니?
아니, 다른 사람은 안돼
-I think this could be "it. "
-Really?
정말?
나 같음 데이빗 핫셀호프
닮은 거 하나로도 결혼하겠다
I'd marry him for his
David Hasselhoff impression alone.
You know I'll be doing that
at parties.
파티에서 이렇게 춤도 추고
그 친구 어떤 점이 제일
맘에 드는지 알아?
-lKnow what I like most?
-What?
뭔데?
The way he makes me feel about myself.
그 친구를 보면 꼭
날 보는 느낌이야
그래...
안녕
게임 어땠어?
How was the game?
그냥...
Well....
우리가 이겼지롱
We won!
잘됐다, 하나만 물을게
어떻게 이긴 거야?
Fantastic! Question.
How is that possible?
- 알란 덕이었지
- 굉장했어
-Alan.
-He was unbelievable!
Like the cartoon where
Bugs Bunny plays every position.
벅스 버니 나오는 만화처럼
이곳저곳 맘대로 누비는 거야
It was first base, Alan.
Second base, Alan....
1루에도 알란, 2루에도 알란,
3루에도 알란...
그 사람이 우릴 한 팀으로
만들어준 거야
It was like he made us into a team.
그럼, 우리가 상대 선수들한테
야구를 똑똑히 가르쳐줬지
We sure showed those Hasidic jewelers
a thing or two about softball.
그렇지
Can I ask a question?
하나 물어봐도 돼?
- 혹시라도 알렌이 너무나...
- 뭐?
Do you think Alan is sometimes....
What?
글쎄, 너무 '알란'적이란
생각이 들지 않아?
I don't know. A little too "Alan"?
천만에, 그런 소리 마
'알란'적이라니
Oh, no. Not possible.
You can never be too "Alan. "
그럼, 그 친구의 숨겨진
'알란'다움을 우린 존중해
It's his innate "Alan-ness"
that we adore.
난 알란이 한 박스만
있으면 좋겠다
I, personally, could have
a gallon of Alan.
안녕, 리지
-Hey, Lizzy.
-Hey, weird girl.
안녕, 괴짜 아가씨
알파벳 수프 가져왔어요
-I brought alphabet soup.
-Pick out the vowels?
- 모음으로 골라왔어?
- 네
I left in the Y's.
Because, "sometimes Y. "
근데 'y'는 빼놓고 왔어요
왜냐면 'y'니까...
다른 것도 가져왔어요
-And something else.
-Saltines?
크래커?
아뇨, 천 달러랑
풋볼 전화기 가질래요?
No, $1 000 and a football phone.
뭐?
What?
Oh, my God!
맙소사, 진짜 돈이잖아
-There's really money in here.
-I know.
알아요
What are you doing?
괴짜 아가씨, 뭐하는 거야?
그냥 아줌마 가지세요
전 싫어요
I want you to have it.
I don't want it.
그럼 나도 아가씨한테
뭐라도 줘야지
-I have to give you something.
-No, you don't
아뇨, 괜찮아요
-Do you want my tinfoil hat?
-No, you need that.
호일 모자 줄까?
아뇨, 아줌마 가지세요
괜찮아요, 고마워요
-It's okay. Thanks.
-Let me do something.
뭐라도 주고 싶어
소다나 하나 사줄래요?
그럼 공평하잖아요
I'll tell you what. Buy me
a soda and we' re even. Okay?
됐죠?
- 좋아
- 그래요
-Okay.
IKeep the change.
잔돈은 가져요
Thanks, Lizzy.
고마워요, 리지
Want a pretzel?
비스킷 정말 안 먹어?
-No, l' m fine. Thanks.
-See you.
네, 괜찮아요
잘 가
A thumb?
엄지손가락?
I know. There it was,
just floating...
그렇다니까, 캔을 땄더니
손가락이 둥둥 떠다니는 거야
...Iike this tiny little hitchhiker.
Maybe it's a contest.
Like "collect all five. "
다섯 손가락 전부 모으기
경품이벤트 같은 거 아닐까?
- 한번 볼래?
- 아니
-Does anyone wanna see?
-No, thanks!
됐어
- 야...
- 그러지 좀 마
Don't do that. Come on!
엄지손가락보다 심하다
It's worse than the thumb.
정말 너무들 한다
-This is so unfair.
-Why is it unfair?
- 뭐가 너무해?
- 정말
그래, 나도 약점이 있다
뭐 어때
So I have a flaw! Big deal!
Joey's knuckle-cracking
isn't annoying?
조이는 항상 말도 안되는
헛소리나 해대고
Ross, over-pronouncing every word.
로스는 단어마다 힘줘서
발음하고
Monica, who snorts when she laughs.
I mean, what the hell is that thing?
모니카는 웃을 때 킁킁거리는데
담배 하나 못 피워?
난 너희들 약점을 인정하는데
너희는 왜 날 못 받아주는데?
I accept those flaws.
Why can't you accept me for this?
내 얘기가 그렇게 썰렁해?
Does the knuckle-cracking
bother everybody, or just him?
안 들어도 살 순 있지
I could live without it.
피비가 머리카락 씹을 때처럼
그렇게 신경쓰여?
Is it a little annoying? Or is it like
when Phoebe chews her hair?
쟤 말 듣지마, 피비
나 보기엔 좋기만 하다
Don't listen to him.
I think it's endearing.
그래? 그러셔?
Oh, you do, do you?
발음을 정확하게 하는 게
뭐가 문제야?
There's nothing wrong with
speaking correctly.
Indeed there isn't.
아무 문제 없지
난 일하러 가야겠다
I should get back to work.
안 그럼 우리 주문대로
정확히 커피를 마실 테니까
Otherwise someone might
get what they ordered.
The hair comes out
and the gloves come off.
머리카락아, 나와라
주먹 들어가신다
친구들이 좋아 죽는 남자랑
사귀어본 적 있어요?
Ever go out with a guy
your friends really like?
No.
아니
내가 사귀는 남자를
친구들이 너무나 좋아해요
I'm going out with a guy
my friends really like.
코요테 친구들 얘기야?
Are we talking about the coyotes here?
좋아, 테스트 통과했군
All right! A cow got through.
기막히지 않아요?
Can you believe it?
It's just, you know what?
전 아무 느낌이 없는데
I just don't feel the "thing. "
걔들은 그게 있나봐요
전 아무 느낌이 없거든요
They feel the thing. I don't feel it.
Honey, you should always
feel the thing.
자기도 느낌을 가져보라구
진짜 아무 느낌이 없으면
남자친구를 차버려야지
If that's how you feel about the guy,
dump him.
쉽지 않을 거예요
-It's gonna be really hard.
-He'll get over it.
다 큰 어른인데
이겨내겠지
아뇨, 남자친구가 아니라
친구들이 걱정이에요
No, he'll be fine. It's the other five
l' m worried about.
-Don't you respect your body?
-Don't you see what you' re doing?
몸이 걱정되지도 않아?
무슨 짓을 하는지
모른단 말야?
암이니 폐병이니 심장병이니
하는 소리 지겹게 들었어
I've had it with your cancer,
emphysema and heart disease.
The bottom line is, smoking is cool,
and you know it.
어쨌든 담배는 좋은 거야
너희도 알잖아
챈들러,
알란이 너 좀 바꿔 달래
Alan wants to speak to you.
정말? 알란이?
Really? He does?
Hey, buddy! What's up?
안녕, 친구, 웬일이야?
모니카한테 들었구나
She told you about that, huh?
Well, yeah. I have one now and then.
Well, yeah, now.
그래, 가끔씩 피워
지금도 피우고
그 정도는 아냐
It's not that
맞는 말이야
Well, that's true.
아무도 그렇게 얘기해준 적
없는데...
Gee, you know, no one's ever put it
like that before.
그래, 고마워
Well, okay. Thanks.
정말 대단한 사람이야
God, he's good.
- 여자면 좋을 텐데
- 그러게
-lf only he were a woman.
-Yeah.
저 양말 얼마나 오래 됐을까
Lamb Chop!
How old is that sock?
If I had a sock on my hand
for 30 years, it'd be talking too.
30년 동안이나 손에 끼워져
있으면 나도 말할 수 있겠다
니코틴 패치를 갈아줘야 할
시간이 됐군
I think it's time to change somebody's
nicotine patch.
안녕
조이 어딨어?
-Where's Joey?
-Joey ate my last stick of gum...
하나 남은 내 껌을 씹길래
내가 죽여버렸어
...so I killed him.
내가 잘못한 거야?
Do you think that was wrong?
-I think he's across the hall.
-Thanks.
- 집에 있을 거야
- 고마워
There you go.
됐어
갑자기 기쁨이 샘솟는다
I'm alive with pleasure now.
피비, 그거 먹을 거야?
피비?
Pheebs, do you want
the rest of that Pop-T art?
이거 누가 먹을래?
Does anyone want
the rest of this Pop-T art?
나
Hey, I might.
I'm sorry.
미안
소다 회사에서 엄지손가락
들어갔다고 7천 달러나 줬어
The soda people gave me $7000
for the thumb.
- 세상에
- 7천 달러?
집에 오는 길엔
껌을 밟아 버렸어
And on my way over here
I stepped in gum.
What is up with the universe?
세상이 어찌 돌아가는 거야?
무슨 일이야?
-What's going on?
-It's just nice when we' re together.
별 일은 아니고 다함께
모여있는 게 좋을 것 같아서
다 속옷만 입고 모이면
더 좋을 뻔했다
It's nicer when everyone
gets to wear underwear.
조이...
좋아
우리, 얘기 좀 해
Please, guys, we have to talk.
잠깐,
언젠가 이런 일이 있었어
Wait! I'm getting a deja vu.
아니, 아니다
No, l' m not.
-We have to talk.
-There it is!
- 좋아, 얘기 좀 해
- 분명히 있었던 일이야
알란에 관해서 인데
Okay, it's about Alan.
잘됐다, 주말에 르네상스 박람회
있다고 전해줄래?
Speaking of which, tell him
we're on for the Renaissance Fair.
- 맞아
- 그 얘기 전에...
Before you get into that,
there's something you should know.
너희가 알아야 할 게 있어
이런 말하기가 쉽지 않은데
There's really no easy way
to say this.
알란이랑 헤어지기로 했어
I've decided to break up with Alan.
Is there somebody else?
다른 사람 생긴 거야?
아니, 상황은 변하게 마련이야
사람은 변한다구
No, it's just...
...you know, things change.
People change.
We didn't change.
우린 안 변했는데
그게 다야?
끝난 거야?
So that's it? It's over?
그렇게 쉽게?
Just like that?
네가 좋아하는 사람을 이제
겨우 우리도 좋아하게 됐는데...
You let your guard down. You start
to care about someone, and....
- 아닌 척할 수도 있어
- 좋아
-I can go on pretending
-Okay!
No.
아니
그건 나한테도 알란한테도
너희한테도 공평하지 못해
That wouldn't be fair to me, Alan,
or to you.
누가 공평하게 해달래?
Well, who wants fair?
원래대로 돌려놔
처음으로 돌려놓으라구
I just want things back, you know,
the way they were.
- 미안해
- 미안하다니 기분이 좀 낫다
-l' m sorry.
-Oh, she's sorry. I feel better.
믿을 수가 없어
곧 휴가철이잖아
I can't believe this!
With the holidays coming up.
I wanted him to meet my family.
가족들 소개하려고 했는데
다른 사람 만날 거야
제 2의 알란이 생길 거라구
I'll meet someone.
There'll be other Alans.
- 말도 안돼
- 행여나
Yeah, right!
-Are you guys gonna be okay?
-We'll be fine.
- 다들 괜찮겠지?
- 괜찮을 거야
시간이 좀 걸릴 뿐이지
We're just gonna need a little time.
알았어
I understand.
-Wow.
-l' m really sorry.
정말 미안해요
나도 미안해요
Yeah, I mean, l' m sorry too.
-But l' m a little relieved.
-Relieved?
하지만 솔직히
좀 안심이 되긴 해요
안심이 돼요?
그래요, 당신과는
좋은 시간을 보냈지만
Yeah, well, I mean,
I had a great time with you.
친구들은 참을 수가
없었거든요
I just can't stand your friends.
Remember when we went to Central Park
and rented boats?
센트럴 파크에서
보트 탔던 거 기억나?
참 재밌었는데
That was fun.
그래, 알란이 바이킹처럼
노를 저었지
He could row like a Viking.
- 안녕
So how'd it go?
어떻게 됐어?
그냥...
You know.
우리 얘기도 해?
Did he mention us?
다들 보고 싶을 거래
He says he's really gonna
miss you guys.
힘들었겠구나
-Rough day, huh?
-You have no idea.
- 오빠는 상상도 못할걸
- 이리 와
Come here.
-That's it. I' m getting cigarettes.
-No!
- 못 참아, 나 담배 피울래
- 안돼
상관없어, 게임 끝났어
난 연약한 놈이야
I don't care! I' m weak!
담배 피울 거야
담배를 피워야겠어
I've gotta have the smoke!
If you never smoke again,
I'll give you $7000.
담배끊으면 7천 달러 줄게
좋아
Yeah, all right.